<?xml version="1.0" encoding="ISO-8859-1" ?>
<rss version="0.91">
<channel>
<title>Book and Book Review Articles at ArticleGeek.com</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com</link>
<description>Book and Book Review Articles Feed From ArticleGeek.com</description>
<language>en-us</language>
<image>
<title>ArticleGeek.com</title>
<url>http://www.articlegeek.com/pictures/logo_88x31.jpg</url>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/pictures/logo_88x31.jpg</link>
<width>88</width>
<height>31</height>
</image>
<item>
<title>Half of a Yellow Sun by Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/14705-halfofyellowsun.htm</link>
<description>Philip Spires, author of Mission, an African novel set in Kenya reviews Half of a Yellow Sun by Chimanada Ngozi Adichie, a novel set in the era of the Biafran war in Nigeria.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Selling Ebooks for Dummies</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/selling_ebooks_dummies.htm</link>
<description>Ebooks. It seems like they have been with us for some time now. At the beginning of digital technology it was predicted that digital books - Ebooks would replace conventional printed books. Obviously this is not going to happen at least not too soon.
But in today's fast online world, convenience of instant delivery and huge supply and variety on the market together with cheaper price - the Ebook is a fantastic product and has its place on the market.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Look at Viral E-books</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/viral_ebooks_look.htm</link>
<description>How ebooks can work like a virus to make money selling your products and services with links to affiliate products.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>How To Break Into The World of Internet Business Without A Website Or Product To Sell</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/internet_business_no_website.htm</link>
<description>In his free ebook  "15 Powerful Ways CBMall Makes Money For You", Jeff Mulligan explains how to add an extra income stream to your existing internet business or even use the CBMall as a stand alone business.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Book Review: The Straw Bale House</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/straw_bale_house_book_review.htm</link>
<description>If a cookie-cutter world of bland, expensive, poorly-insulated, mass-produced tract homes doesn't quite appeal to you, the book: The Straw Bale House might just serve as the inspiration necessary to escape the mundane.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Book Review: The Bottomless Well: Why We Will Never Run Out of Energy</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/bottomless_well_book_review.htm</link>
<description>Do environmentalists have a monopoly on our world view of energy consumption?  What if our consumption of energy is not the problem, but rather the actual solution to the problems we face?  The Bottomless Well presents an alternative view of the complex energy picture.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>The Deepest Secrets To E-books</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/ebook_deepest_secrets.htm</link>
<description>The deepest Secrets behind e-books  finally revealed. If you want to know how they make it, you'll definitely need to know what they're doing.</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Proven Secrets of Writing and Publishing Your Own eBook... In Less Than a Week!</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/ebook_writing_publishing_week.htm</link>
<description>In one week you could have your own highly profitable ebook published and on the web!</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>A Simple, Easy, Legitimate Way to Get FREE Traffic to Your Site!</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/get_free_website_traffic.htm</link>
<description>Take The Guesswork Out Of Writing Articles</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Book Review:  Manners That Sell</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/manners_that_sell_review.htm</link>
<description>Manners That Sell:  Adding The Polish That Builds Profits focuses on business etiquette that makes the difference between getting the sale and losing the client.  No longer taught in school, Manners That Sell, covers essential etiquette topics that will help you and your company grow and thrive!</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Are audio books expensive?</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/are_audio_books_expensive.htm</link>
<description>Are audio books expensive? Well, it's a tough question. What kind of audio books - downloaded audio books, audio books on CD or books on tape, which titles? And compared to what - the old fashioned book or to other audio titles?  Let us examine the prices and then take a look at the factors that affect the price of audio books...</description>
</item>


<item>
<title>Online audio book rental services - Who needs it anyway?</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles/online_audio_book_rental.htm</link>
<description>So what exactly are these online audio book rental services and will you get benefit from them? Read on and find out the answers for your questions...</description>
</item>

<item>
<title>Latest Book and Book Review Articles at ArticleGeek.com</title>
<link>http://www.articlegeek.com/shopping/books_articles.htm</link>
<description>Read the latest Book and Book Review Articles from ArticleGeek.com</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>